<resources>
    <string name="app_name">IELTS Assistance</string>
    //listening
    <string name="listening">The IELTS Listening Test is the first part of the exam. It  approximately 30 minutes (plus 10 minutes transfer time) and the test format consists of 4 sections and a total of 40 questions. The Listening test is the same for both Academic and General Training tests.\nThere are four sections:\n</string>
    <string name="ql">"Section 1 is a conversation between two people set in an everyday context (e.g. a conversation in an accommodation agency)\n

Section 2 is a monologue set in an everyday social context (e.g. a speech about local families).\n

Section 3 is a conversation between up to four people set in an educational or training context (e.g. a university tutor and student discussing an assignment).\n

Section 4 is a monologue on an academic subject (e.g. a university lecture).\n
</string>

    <string name="tips_lis">"
1.Improve your general listening skills\n
2.identify your listening weaknesses and work on improving those areas.\n
3.Polish your topic vocabulary\n
4.Try to get an idea of the situation\n
5.Don't loose attention\n
6.Check for silly mistakes\n
7.Watch out words-indicators\n
8.Don't write answers too quickly\n
9.Transfer answers accurately\n
10.Don't leave any blank answers\n</string>

    /// for reading
    <string name="reading">
        You will be allowed 1 hour to complete all 3 sections of the IELTS Academic Reading test.There are 40 questions in this practice paper.The total text length is 2,150-2,750 words.Each question carries one mark.\n\n</string>


    <string name="qr">"
-Each section contains one long text.\n
-Texts are authentic and are taken from books, journals, magazines and newspapers. They have been written for a non-specialist audience and are on academic topics of general interest.\n
-Texts are appropriate, and accessible, to test-takers entering undergraduate or postgraduate courses, or seeking professional registration.\n
-Texts range from descriptive and factual to the discursive and analytical.\n
-Texts may contain non-verbal materials, such as diagrams, graphs or illustrations.\n
-texts contain technical terms, a simple glossary is provided.\n</string>
    <string name="tip_read">
        Develop skills of each type of question in reading. There are around 14 different types of questions and you need to find a strategy to tackle each one\n
1.Skimming and Scanning\n
2.Develop your speed reading skills\n
3.Do not try to understand the full passage\n
4.Developing vocabulary\n
5.key words\n
6.Grammar\n
7.Do not over-analyze\n
8understand collocations (matching verbs with nouns)\n
9.avoid spelling mistakes\n
10.Read the instructions and the examples carefully \n</string>
    <string name="writing">There are two tasks. Candidates are required to write at least 150 words for Task 1 and at least 250 words for Task 2.
Both responses should be written in a formal style.This Writing test is 60 minutes long.\n\n

    </string>
    <string name="qw">IELTS Writing Task1 \n\n
The Writing Task 1 of the IELTS Academic test requires you to write a summary of at least 150 words in
response to a particular graph (bar, line or pie graph), table, chart, or process (how something works, how something is done).
 This task tests your ability to select and report the main features, to describe and compare data, identify significance and trends in factual information,
 or describe a process.\n\n
IELTS Writing Task 2\n\n
The five most common IELTS Writing Task 2 questions are: Opinion (Agree or Disagree) Advantages and Disadvantages. Problem and Solution.\n
    Some of the IELTS writing questions could of course be in more than one topic area.\n\n
* Animals.\n
* Culture and Traditions.\n
* Health, Fitness and Diet.\n
* Media.\n
* Technology.\n
* Science.\n
    </string>

    <string name="trip_writing">"
1.Understand the requirements of both tasks\n
2.Before writing an essay, you must know its basic structure\n
3.Do Task 2 first, because it is worth more marks and is easier.\n
4.Do not waste too much time on Task 1\n
5.You must complete both tasks\n
6.Writing requires wide academic vocabulary.\n
7.Plan. Before writing, carefully read and consider all prompt material.\n
8.Analyse Graphs and Charts.\n
9.Write convincing essays.\n
10.Improve your English.\n
</string>

    ///speaking
    <string name="speaking">The Speaking test is as close to a real-life situation as an exam can get.
You will talk to a certified examiner in the IELTS Speaking test. The test is interactive and as close to a real-life situation as a test can get. A variety of accents may be used, and the test will be recorded.
The content of the IELTS Speaking test is the same for both the IELTS Academic and IELTS General Training tests.This test takes 11-14 minutes.\n\n</string>
    <string name="qs">" The Speaking test consists of three parts:
    Task 1: You will be asked to answer general questions about yourself and a range of familiar
    topics, such as your home, family, work, studies and interests. This part lasts between 4 and 5
    minutes.\n
    Task 2: You will be given a card and you will be asked to talk about a particular topic. You
    will have one minute to prepare before speaking for up to two minutes.\n
    Task 3: You will be asked further questions connected to the topic in Part 2. These questions
    give you an opportunity to discuss more abstract issues and ideas. This part lasts between four
    and five minutes\n</string>

    <string name="tipspeaking">"
Follow this Speaking test advice and try to talk fluently.
1.try to talk as much as you can.\n
2.talk as fluently as possible and be spontaneous.\n
3.relax, be confident and enjoy using your English.\n
4.develop your answers.\n
5.speak more than the examiner.\n
6.ask for clarification if necessary.\n
7.Practice Speaking in Real Life Situations.\n
8.Set Your Target and Make a Timeline\n
9.Prepare For the IELTS Speaking Test by Listening and Reading\n
10.Learn From Your Mistakes\n</string>


    <string name="answer">
        <a href="https://ieltsliz.com/">Writing answer</a>
    </string>
    <string name="facebook">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/-/media/pdfs/general-writing-answer-sheet-task-1.ashx?la=en">facebook</a>
    </string>
    /// Resource
<string name="r1">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/">1. The official Website of IELTS</a>
    </string>
<string name="r2">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/book-a-test/find-a-test-location">2. Find a Test center near your</a>
    </string>
<string name="r3">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/book-a-test/how-do-i-register">3. How do I register?</a>
    </string>
<string name="r4">
        <a href="https://howtospell.co.uk/spellingquiz.php">4. Listening Practice </a>
    </string>
<string name="r5">
        <a href="https://howtospell.co.uk/spellingquiz.php">5. Spelling practice </a>
    </string>
<string name="r6">
        <a href="https://www.englisch-hilfen.de/en/exercises_list/alle_grammar.htm">6. Grammar practice </a>
    </string>
<string name="r7">
        <a href="https://www.englisch-hilfen.de/en/exercises_list/alle_grammar.htm">7. Basic Pronunciation practice  </a>
    </string><string name="r8">
        <a href="https://www.bbc.co.uk/news/world">8. BBBC World news  </a>
    </string><string name="r9">
        <a href="https://www.newscientist.com/">9. For Reading (News Science)  </a>
    </string>
    <string name="r10">
        <a href="https://www.nationalgeographic.com/">10 For Reading (National geography) </a>
    </string>
    <string name="answerL">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/-/media/360886d7438541f28295ab83f07a0ef9.ashx">ILETS Listening Answer Sheet  </a>
    </string>
    <string name="answerR">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/-/media/pdfs/general-reading-answer-sheet.ashx?la=en">ILETS Reading Answer Sheet  </a>
    </string>
    <string name="answerR1">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/-/media/pdfs/academic-writing-answer-sheet-task-1.ashx?la=en">ILETS writing task-1 answer Sheet  </a>
    </string>
    <string name="answeR2">
        <a href="https://www.ielts.org/-/media/pdfs/general-writing-answer-sheet-task-2.ashx?la=en">ILETS writing task-2 answer Sheet  </a>
    </string>

</resources>



